foreign
uh
yes
street
um
we are
uh
oh
there's
wow
how's it going you're fine
foreign
so
oh
we are in here
is
right
okay
easy
um
oh oh
oh
we can always just walk down
okay
please
about two to two fifty
there's 75
oh
uh
foreign
hey guys i'm just following them around
for right now i'm gonna leave this thing
i'm gonna leave this thing going
continuously then periscope if it gets
heated or whatever
feel free to tweet out this link send
out the link wherever
oh
here
i love it
uh
okay
so
oh my gosh
cyrus
today is
like you are out there
hey
bye
uh
keep touching the snake bubbles
um
we're gonna meet out there
good lt i know you like it you wish you
could have one like this
you know
foreign
ah necessary
is
in the shadows
up
oh
so i'm pretty sure
sorry
oh
foreign
is
it is not just for me it's for the legal
muslims in china across the world
foreign
we should be able to ask
oh
like two hours ago
somebody
oh yeah
you know it's a community
thank you
hey
hello
oh
um
theresa
my god
i thought
you
if you got it over here
hey
i don't know
preparing yourself for back in november
thank you for preparing ourselves to get
donald trump out the office
thank y'all for changing not only for
the national government
but
november not only for the president
remember when you leave here
one more time make sure you spread that
energy spread this energy
because he knows that black and white
are getting
shot and killed orlando's not doing
anything about it all right
he knows that donald trump knows that
people are dying right
that's our person knows that he's not
about it so
your first job is
is very close this
come on
you have to encourage
all right i'm gonna sign off for a
minute because i'm gonna go look around
for some other groups
come back i'll be back
share this link